CANDICE MARTINS

UX DESIGNER

A UX Designer with a strong passion for design strategy, colour, and iconography.

Strive to meet the user's needs by putting myself in the user's shoes, creating new ideas and solving issues that initially seem impossible.

9766417072

- candicem1810@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/candicanza
- Bē https://www.behance.net/CandiCanza

Design Projects

UI/UX DESIGNER Cakebusters

Mar 2022- Present

Designed a mobile app with a hassle-free pickup and delivery experience for bakery lovers where they can order online with the different payment methods and pick it up at their own convenient time or quickly get a fast delivery service.user interviews, competitive analysis, storyboarding, sketching, wireframing and prototyping using Figma.

UI/UX DESIGNER Rebook (Reuse the book)

Jan 2022 - May 2022

Designed a mobile app which enhanced the experience of book lovers by providing them with the unique feature of a preview video of the secondhand book before purchasing it. Conducted user interviews, user journey mapping, and heuristic evaluation and created an interactive prototype using Figma.

SKILLS

- User Design
 - Persona
 - Story Boarding
- Sketching
- Wireframing
 - Heuristic Evalution
 - Prototyping

Certificates

 Google UX Design Professional at Coursera Mar 2022-Present

UX UI Design from Scratch at Designerrs Academy

Jan 2022-May 2022

Figma

Tools



XD



WORK EXPERIENCE

ASSOCIATE IT

TATA STEEL LTD,BOISAR

Jun 2021-Feb 2022

Solving the user's problems by creating new form and report per the user's requirement, working on SAP and PLSQL and debugging the Oracle forms and reports to solve the user problem.

BDE

E-FREEBESS PVT LTD,VIKHROLI

Jan 2021-May 2021

Providing softwares demos for the companies listed with BSE or NSE all over India. completing the target daily by arranging the timeslots for the CA of the respective companies to join us for a demo and who is willing to purchase the software.

GRADUATE APPRENTICE TATA STEEL LTD, BOISAR

Aug 2019-Aug 2020

Worked on Oracle forms and report builder and created a report that would help the accounts department find the the annual cost for the entire month of the coils and provide an excel download option to that report.

EDUCATION

University of Mumbai
Bachelor of Computer Science

2014-2019